puzzlezoo.com 2015-10-26

# Security & Privacy | ToyZoo.com

This is the Security & Privacy Policy page for ToyZoo.com. We take our customer's personal information very seriously and never use it for any other reason than to provide you with the best possible service and security.

This Privacy Policy explains the manner in which ToyZoo.com collects personal data from you and the purpose for that collection. This Privacy Policy is designed to ensure that you are aware of how your personal data is being used and to provide you with choices about that use. By visiting the ToyZoo.com website or submitting your personal data, you accept the terms described in this Privacy Policy. From time to time we may modify these rules. Your continued use of ToyZoo.com after any modification indicates your agreement to the new terms.

_Last Revised: February, 2013_

## How do you protect my personal information?

At ToyZoo.com, we realize that there is no greater concern to our customers than the security of their personal and payment information. We are proud to say that the privacy and security of your information is a top priority. ToyZoo.com utilizes 256-bit SSL encryption and is certified by GoDaddy.com. We are committed to keeping your private information just that: private.

Return to Top

## What, exactly, is SSL encryption?

SSL stands for Secured Sockets Layer. The 256-bit encryption essentially means that any information you provide us with is encrypted (encoded and scrambled) in a way that no third party could read it, were they to intercept its transmission. The information can be decrypted or "de-scrambled" by ToyZoo.com using a special software key only entrusted to us.

Return to Top

## What kind of information do you collect about me?

To place an order, there are several pieces of information we need to process and ship your items, including your shipping and billing addresses and credit card information. The required information for an order can be found on our Order Help Page page.

Return to Top

## How will my information be used?

Your information will only be used for the purposes of enhancing your buying experience at ToyZoo.com. If you have chosen to opt in to our e-mail list to receive promotional notifications, we may use this information to personalize your communications.

Return to Top

## Do you share my information with anyone else?

Absolutely not. We understand that your are providing your information to ToyZoo.com for the purpose of ordering from or interacting with us, and no one else. Under no circumstances do we give, trade or sell your personal information to any other entity or company.

Return to Top

## How do I change my personal information?

You can always edit, update, or delete information from your user profile by logging in to your account through ToyZoo.com. Simply click on the "Your Account" button which is located in the upper-right corner of the ToyZoo.com website. Once logged in, the secure connection allows you to make any changes you wish with total safety. For step-by-step instructions for making these changes, visit our [Account Help](http://www.toyzoo.com/account-help) area.

If you choose to make changes to your account via phone or fax, you may do so. However these changes may not take immediate effect since they must be entered by the customer service representative who helps you. When you contact us by phone, our customer service representative will need to verify your identity by asking for the e-mail address, password, and phone number on record. However, if you are contacted by ToyZoo.com, via e-mail or phone, we will NEVER ask for your password or other sensitive information.

Return to Top

## What about other links and websites?

The ToyZoo.com website is linked to several other websites, including the Better Business Bureau, GoDaddy.com (our security provider), and others. Additionally, several other sites may have links which direct users to us. However, neither the connections into nor out of our website have access to any of your information, and your privacy and security are in no way compromised by these connections. Furthermore our parent company, PuzzleZoo, Inc. does not share any customer information with these or any other entities.

Return to Top

## Statistical Tracking using Browser Cookies

ToyZoo.com uses Google Analytics, Google AdWords Conversion tracker, and other Google services that place cookies on a browser across the website. These cookies help us increase the website's effectiveness for our visitors. These cookies are set and read by Google. To opt out of Google Tracking, please visit [this page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

We use Google AdWords remarketing to market our site across the web. We place a cookie on a browser, and then a 3rd party (Google) reads these cookies and may serve an ad on a 3rd party site. You may opt out of this ad serving on Google's opt out page. If you are concerned about 3rd party cookies served by networks, you should also visit the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Return to Top

## Why Do I Have To Re-enter My Credit Card Information on my Pre-Order?

ToyZoo.com complies with industry standards that protect you the customer. ToyZoo.com does not have access to credit card information when the initial order is made. All credit card information is sent directly to our credit card processor and it is not stored on any device or program ToyZoo.com can access. When an order is approved, the only information ToyZoo.com receives is the type of credit card used as well as the last four digits of the card. If more than a few days have passed between the time the initial purchase was placed and when the pre-ordered items are prepared to ship out, the credit card authorization will have expired and the credit card information will have to be entered in again before we can ship the order out.

Return to Top

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.toyzoo.com/contacts).
